(Leonard:)rubbing our success
in Sheldon's face.
(Raj:)Oh, well, that's
the best part.
Oh, yeah.
(Bernadette:)Dan, could I talk
to you for a minute?
(Dan:)Sure, go ahead.
(Bernadette:)Just want you to know
I didn't mean
(Bernadette:)to be rude about your grandson.
(Dan:)No, it's okay.
(Sheldon:)No, it's not.
(Bernadette:)Penny told me
that everyone's scared of me.
(laughing):
What? What?
(Dan:)Why would she say that?
(Dan:)You know she drinks, right?
(Bernadette:)What?
(Bernadette:)No, she's right,
and I just want you to know
(Bernadette:)that from now on, I'm gonna be
much more sensitive.
(Bernadette:)I don't want anyone walking
on eggshells around me.
(Dan:)Oh, well, okay, then, uh,
(Dan:)one thing
I've been meaning to tell you
(Dan:)is that the company is gonna
stop paying for our coffee.
(Bernadette:)No problem. When
does that start?
(Dan:)Five months ago.
What?!
Yeah.
(Bernadette:)Who's been paying
for my coffee?
(Dan:)All of us.
(Penny:)Yeah. It comes
from the swear jar
(Penny:)we put money in when you curse.
(Bernadette:)What else don't I know about?